Hey everyone, this is Sean. Today I want
to introduce you to agent team and agent
swarm. These are two of the latest AI
agents concepts. We're going to walk you
through the system design real quick and
then we're going to test it with the
products out there on the market. Just
in January, Kim AI launched a new model
called K2.5 where they introduced their
agent swarm product feature which can
help you break down your task into 100
sub pages that will work in parallel.
And then shortly after that in February,
Claude Opus 4.6 was launched. And then
they also made a huge update on
introducing agent teams in claw code.
These two are not exactly the same
concepts. Doesn't matter if you're
technical or not. I'm going to introduce
these things to you very clearly. And
then we're going to test two products at
the same time with the same problem to
see which one does a better job at
breaking down task. And lastly, we're
also going to quickly talk about the
difference between team swarm and deep
research agent. There's a quite a bit of
similarities and differences. So it's
going to be a really fun video. Let's
get started. So normally when we talk
about AI agent, we can start with a
single agent. Basically, you can imagine
you're talking to chat GBT where you're
sending a user prompt. You can say,
"Help me research who is the best AI
builder and YouTuber on the internet and
then the LM agent from Chat GBT will be
processing this information and they'll
be using a tool for example a search API
to look on the internet and maybe they
find Sean is the best AI builder and
YouTuber on the internet." So that's
finishes one task for a single agent and
then things can get a little bit more
complicated. We can introduce a
sequential agent. After the user asks
the first question, they can send that
to a research agent first and it's going
to pass down the contact that it has
researched to the next agent called
analysis agent which probably will do a
lot of processing after you know the
research online. And after the analysis
agent has finished, it's probably going
to call a report agent which will write
the report for you. You can think of it
as just a sequential workflow that would
happen in a lot of daily life and daily
work. Okay. One problem with sequential
agents is that they're doing things one
by one and there's an order there. So
sometimes it could take a really long
time or maybe you want to you know
increase the capacity of work. So that's
why agent teams comes really handy.
Clocko is basically using a leader agent
first to process this new prompt and
then the leader agent is going to think
what can it do to make this such a
thorough and nice report. What you can
do is that you can define a few agents
in parallel at the same time to process
different tasks. The leader agent has
control over all of them just like the
deep research agent. You might have
realized that in deep research when the
user asks a question they're going to
clarify the question with you and then
they're going to write a research brief.
there's going to be a supervisor agent
that will be you know the leader agent
here and then delegate all the tasks to
the subress researchers over here right
so this part I would say is very similar
uh but it's not entirely the same right
because agent teams doesn't really have
you know some predefined clarification
and research brief all these little
workers are you know doing things in
parallel at the same time and then
report back to the leader agent at this
time the leader agent is really being
the boss here the team lead that's why
it's called agent teams this team lead
is going to process all the information
that the subtask that you know my
workers have done for me. So what is an
agent swarm then? Imagine you have a
bunch of bees in a hive to work for the
queen and then the queen is basically
processing a user prompt. There's a goal
agent that will help derive some of the
goals and specs that you know this user
actually wants right again who's the
best AI YouTuber on the internet.
They're going to say okay the goal is
let me find like the top 20 YouTubers
who do a lot of really good videos
covering AI agent systems. And then
you're going to define some subtask or
even create some agents with templates
by itself. You see the difference here
is that this goal agent is creating
agents templates by itself. Each little
one of these smaller agents are actually
created right there instead of defined
previously. Okay. In agent teams, you
have to define who's doing the research,
who's doing the analysis and everything
and then report back. But in an agent
swarm scenario, simply deciding, okay,
maybe I need 20 agents and each one of
them should be doing certain things.
there's no human involvement there. I
don't need to tell it who should be
doing what, right? So that's why you see
like a swarm here for people who study
machine learning. It's kind of like a
random forest where you have like little
sub trees to make decisions on say
classifying if an image is a dog or a
cat. And then basically the system is
just spawning some parallel agents or
parallel sub trees to um finish the
task. Eventually, you're going to
crowdsource uh the information with a
synthesizer agent, which is basically
like the final layer of a random forest
model where they're going to say, "Okay,
um each one of you has done certain
jobs. Let me compile them together." And
they eventually, you know, cluster the
information together and then merge them
into a deliverable that will become your
output. So this was a quick overview
from single agent to sequential agents
to a team of agents with team lead to an
agent swarm where there's simply a goal
der and then just let the rest of the
work done by a bunch of agents
themselves without any definitions. And
I think agent swarm would excel at a lot
of tasks that would require a lot of
parallel task processing without a lot
of predefin. And that's very powerful
because sometimes you might just have a
really vague intent when you ask a
question to an AI, right? you wanted to
figure out how to break down tasks by
itself. But at the same time, I think it
depends on the task. If your task
requires a lot of like determined
workflow and you want the agent system
or the agent organizations to run
exactly the way you want, like you're
the board member or you're the CEO, then
I think agent teams would do a really
good task because you can have full
control on who's doing what. But I would
say both systems have really good batch
processing features here because they
will allow you to do multiple tasks at
the same time. For example, you can
imagine they can do they might be doing
search, downloading, batch processing
files, talking to different agents uh
all at the same time, which will save
you so much time, but it could also
consume a lot of tokens too. Unlike
these simpler agent systems, teams or
swarm allow a bunch of agents to have
different opinions because they could
have a different conclusion
individualistically. And then eventually
what they do is that either the leader
agent or the synthesizer agent need to
compile reconciliate the decision-m so
that they can come up with a solution
that is not you know uh super biased.
Right? All of what I just explained were
quite theoretical. Let's jump right in
and test the products and see what
happens. The first demo I want to try is
to do a YouTube search. You should be
searching similar channels like Sean's
AI stories. explore those channels that
do developer tools, automation
creations, indie hacking, all these kind
of things. And the result is that I want
them to return four channels uh with
their names and URLs. And the very
similar prompt for claw code is that
you're using agent teams and the context
the same, but then you can be more
specific teammate 1 2 3 4 5 what they're
doing. So I have just pasted both
prompts in claw code and in Kimmy. So
let's get started and run it. All right.
You can see that it shows agent swarm
over there. Okay, cool. Let's see. You
can see that clock understood that it's
running a agent team and it's
establishing shared framework for
strategy editor. Okay. Oh, and then uh
what Kim is doing is that it's creating
all these little agent by itself without
my definition. You see this one is doing
a research agent. This is really cool.
They have this um role description.
You're a competitive intelligence
researcher specializing in AI coding.
And then there are research agents too.
Um you are a competitive intelligence
researcher specializ AI agent automation
content creators.
And this one is searching for educators
I would say I think. Yeah, they're
specializing in AI education. Okay. So
he created these sub agents in parallel
uh like a swarm and then you can see
what they're doing one by one. Okay.
Lewis is doing some uh searching a
YouTube AI SAS solarreneur MR revenue.
Jane who's looking for uh YouTube
channels focus on AI education
explaining uh is doing the following
task. See all of these were written by
um by Kimi itself. This is really cool.
Uh, and then let's see claw code. It
deployed all five scouts in parallel
with the task mainly web search and it's
using tools. I can see exactly what they
looked up for. All right, this YouTuber
uh I don't know who this is.
Kimmy has spent a lot of time polishing
their UI so that it looks very neat and
um you can see what each agent is
actually doing and then check out their
results. This is very similar to how
Chajbt was doing deep research I think
where they will show you exactly what
they're searching. I think Grock also
has similar features where they will
show very clearly and streaming it uh
how how the agent is doing the internet
search whereas if you're doing clock
code in the terminal I think the the UI
is quite minimum but I would say I would
say that's fine because clock code is
mainly focused on coding tasks. Looks
like Jane has finished her task. Let's
see. Jane, find four YouTube channels
focused on education. The final answer
is they found four YouTube channels
focused on AI education. Robert Miles,
Jeremy Howard, Weights and Biases, AI
Uncovered, and then generated a file. I
think I made a mistake because I was
supposed to say five agents here.
Somehow I put 12 and clock doing five.
So, I think we're using a lot more
tokens on uh Kimi. Four, five, six,
seven, eight. Eight out of 12 agents are
finished. I think I'm going to tell Claw
Code, don't overthink.
Let's
focus on letting the scouts
do the basic research. We don't need to
use
more than 10 tools. How come you guys
took such a long time? Oh, this one is
searching like foreign languages. That's
why non-English channel. That's why it's
taking him one time.
Oh, look at this. It's like reading the
channel real time. Took my request now.
Got it. Simplifying. Scout one and two
already back. Let me launch the
remaining three scouts now with learner
instructions. Four channels max minimum
tool usage. Look at this. It took my
feedback. It was done. Scout 3 teammate
3 searching for founder building public
channels. Only use three tools. 15,000
tokens. Previously it was like 70 80
tools was 90,000 tokens. Uhhuh. Looks
like both of them are finished.
10 of 12 agents completed successfully.
Now compiling findings. Look at this. is
compiling the findings and launch
clustering agent. Remember we talked
about the synthesizer. That's that's
what it's doing. Uh because it has
finished the swarm and now they're crowd
they're processing the crowdsourced
information with the synthesizer or it's
calling it launch a clustering agent.
Okay. And clustering agent is Bowwin.
Okay. Bowen, you're analyzing the
competitive landscape for this
and research data.
Okay. So, you see like all of these
researched channels from other um swarm
agents
have been used by this clustering
synthesizer. It clustered 26 channels by
positioning formats. All scouts are back
now synthesizing a strategy editor as
strategy editor lead. So this is this
one is returning the information back to
the lead agent remember and then he's
duping the clustering and um producing
the final deliverable the competitive
landscape shown AI stories. Okay, this
final report already
honestly it's a little hard to read this
from a terminal. It took 20 minutes in
total. 18 minutes 14 seconds. Yeah, it
told me things that other people are not
doing. This is helpful. Um non-English
practical builder content. The Spanish
market has explainer and news, but no
hands-on ship AI product from zero
channel. Okay, maybe that's a good idea.
Every channel shows happy path. Nobody
documents what broke. Oh, yeah. Yeah,
everyone's showing what's working, but
nothing's not working. Um, people don't
show their failures. Okay, fair enough.
Nobody's doing systematic applies to
applies test. Same use case built NN
Langraph.
Every creator picks one tool and
advocates for it. Impartial comparison
seat is empty. That's what we're doing.
We're comparing two tools today. And uh
next video concept for Sean's AI
stories. I built the same agent in Fry
Frameworks. Why my AI agent broke in
production
0 to 10K AI SAS stack. Clocko versus
cursor versus windsurf. Windsor is dead.
No. Um I automated Well, they're not
dead. They're required by by Devon, but
I haven't heard from them ever since. I
automated my entire YouTube workflow
with AI agents. Okay, not a bad report.
At least I real I know at least I
learned that in the Spanish speaking
market, there's not a lot of channels
for hands-on building. Okay, some of our
customers for Automanis, which is a
WhatsApp first Asian sales lead uh tool
has customer from Latin America and uh
they're mainly speaking Spanish and
Portuguese. So, that's a really good uh
good advice. I like that. Okay, look at
this. I think Bowen now is writing the
report. Cool. Look at this. This one's
done. Uh so Kimi was telling me
developer and coder is oversaturated. I
agree. Non-technical founders under
saturating
public founder is moderate. Uh business
automation is underserved. AI education
is moderate. Okay. So probably this one
is suggesting that I should focus on
nontechnical founders and business
automation. Three whites space
opportunities. Cool. Asian workflows for
non-developers.
Okay. Nontechnical founders.
Rigorous tool comparison. This one is
consistent with what Claude told me.
Yeah. The impartial comparison seat is
empty. Asian workflow case studies
theory heavy real metrics rare for
founders and business owners. Okay.
Money related things. Okay. Sure.
Comparing cursor wins co-pilot. How I
built a 4,000 per month uh yeah agency
in 90 days. At least I learned something
which is there is probably an
oversaturation of highly technical
content and um there lacks a lot of uh
AI contents that help educate
non-technical founders or business
owners and uh perhaps I need to compare
some tools because every video is
probably very deep dive in one tool and
also people love money related contents
and last but not least I think in Latin
America there's lack of supply of such
content. Good advice. Thank you both
agent teams from claw code and agent
swarm from Kimmy. And meanwhile I was
running the second demo at the same time
which is a expert review of my uh
current company automatis. We basically
are an WhatsApp first AI sales agent for
consultative made to order sales. You
can imagine like uh companies that are
selling some complex solutions like an
agency or consulting agencies or you
know they could be doing B2B sales like
in um renewable energiesarmacies
uh these things are really complex sales
or even apparel where there's not like a
single SKU to be sold. Sometimes there's
there needs to be a package of like the
entire quantity that you need for
certain products and maybe you need to
customize a little bit. So that's what
we're building um to use agents to
capture all these requests for a
business so that they won't miss any
leads. Okay. So now what I'm doing is
that I want to ask agent swarm from Kimi
and agent team from call code give me
some feedback. For example in teams I
was asking for five teammates to tell me
about my product from VC's perspective
product go to market customer success
and legal. They eventually gave me a
report. Okay. And I was uh running it
and this is surprisingly really fast.
Okay, it's almost done. Okay, it gave me
some advice about pricing. Uh you should
start flat SAS track qualify lead volume
internally introduce per lead pricing in
month three once you can define qualify
with data. That's true. Our investors
gave us similar advice which is uh later
if you have bigger clients what we
should do is uh charge our clients based
on the percentage of conversion but
initially we can do flat pricing which
is um $200 $300 a month design
architecture to be channel agnostic but
doesn't build SMS in week one okay yeah
SMS is probably used only in the US uh
the rest of the world use what's a lot
more so Kimmy had five agents Owen was
evaluating my product well each one
everyone's eval made product. What's
strong already is that WhatsApp channel
selection is strategically sound. 2
billion users. That's true. Two billion
users. Huge market. Made to order
vertical target is smart. Yeah, because
we talked to so many made to order
businesses and um their sales process is
a huge mess. Okay. The risk is
defensibility is thin. Uh yeah, sure.
There's a lot of WhatsApp agents. That's
why we're doing a lot of um sort of lead
structuring as well after talking with
just agents. is not just another
chatbot. Some final comments. Um, I
think AI has been evolving
to mimic how human societies and human
organizations collaborate because I
remember listening to a podcast the
other day that
the way to function really well in the
human society is that there is a team of
specialized workers like you and me who
will be good at, you know, things that
we're good at and uh, collaborating
together. That's how we make the economy
runs. And now we're at the position
where coding agent is really strong.
Tachibbt general agent is really strong.
There are a lot of models that are very
specialized at what they do. And what we
can do is create agent that specialize
in what they do too. Okay. So what I see
is that we're seeing a trend or a shift
from simple AI agents or simple AI agent
systems to AI organizations or AI
societies.
and all of these concepts of whether
it's a swarm from Kimmy or teams from
claw code in my opinion it's
trying to balance the breadth
um of the amount of information that the
decision makers could get in order to
make the best possible decisions rather
than relying on one specific agent to
make a decision at the end. Okay. And
similarly in deep research agent is not
just the decision maker which is
clarification agent, research brief
agent and supervisor agent are making
the decision without asking anybody
else's opinion. Instead they spread it
out and delegate the task to every
single researcher and compress them and
compile them and synthesize the final
output in order to make a more educated
information decision-m. Okay, I feel
like this is a general trend and all
these model providers have realized that
this is a trend and that's why they're
making these products for us. I would
encourage everyone to try this out
because uh when new technology comes
out, it's important that we feel aware
of what's going on. I think the results
definitely are decent for now if we're
doing some, you know, research, building
some features on a product. And I think
they will take another couple of years
or maybe just a few months that it will
evolve into something that's much more
holistic at doing tasks. So what we all
can do right now is make sure we don't
lag behind and that we're always
informed about uh what is going on with
all these uh architecture or infrawise
updates from these top AI companies.
Thanks for watching this video. I hope
this was helpful and leave a comment or
join our Discord channel for a
discussion. I'll see you next time.
Thank you very